<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>

<!--
Copyright 2014-2015 CyberVision, Inc.

  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  
  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  
  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
-->

<projectsConfig>
    <project id="cityguide_demo">
        <name>City guide</name>
        <description>City guide Android app demonstrates Kaa endpoint profiling, grouping, and configuration management capabilities</description>
        <details>
            <![CDATA[
This simple Android app illustrates how Kaa configuration management system can be used to deliver custom-tailored contents to endpoints depending on their profile.

<h2>Installation</h2>
Download the .apk to your Android device by clicking the "Binary" button on the left. Make sure that the device permits installing apps from "Unknown sources". Open the downloaded apk and follow the on-screen instructions.

<h2>Playing around</h2>
Make sure that the Kaa sandbox is up and running. Opening the "City Guide Demo" app will lead you to the nested lists of areas, cities, and places of interest currently visible to the app. You can limit the visibility by choosing a specific area and city in a dialogue available by pressing a "SET LOCATION" button in the upper right corner.<br/><br/>

To understand better how this works, you should navigate to the Kaa server administrative interface by clicking on the "Administrative console" link from the Sandbox screen. Log in as a tenant developer (devuser / devuser123), and go to to the "City guide" application, then select "Schemas", "Profile". Choosing the profile schema version 2 in the list will allow inspecting the contents of the profile that the app sends to Kaa server. It contains two values: area and city. Kaa server uses these values to filter endpoints by their profiles contents and make only relevant content visible to the app.<br/><br/>

Now open the "Configuration" schema under "Schemas" and select version 2 to see the structure of the configuration data. There are two arrays in the configuration schema: "availableAreas" and "areas". The former defines the list of areas available under the "SET LOCATION" dialogue that goes into the endpoint profile. The latter defines the content of the main app screen, including the points of interest and their descriptions.<br/><br/>

Finally, it's time to see how the configuration data is composed. To do so, go to the "Endpoint groups" section. There are three endpoint groups.<br/><br/>

Group "all" configuration defines the list of available for selection areas and cities ("availableAreas").<br/><br/>

"North America/Atlanta" and "Europe/Amsterdam" groups apply to the endpoints which have the corresponding area and city in the profile. (It also applies to endpoints with unset profile). Observe the corresponding profile filters in the group details screen. The configuration associated with these two groups defines the contents displayed for the areas of interest in these locations. Feel free to open the configuration data for schema version 2 and browse the configuration body. You are also welcome to <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Administration+UI+guide#AdministrationUIguide-Addconfigurationtoendpointgroup">make your changes to the configuration</a> and see how the updates get propagated to your Android device.

Please note that all features of <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Administration+UI+guide">Administrative UI</a> are also supported by <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Admin+REST+API">REST API</a>.

<h2>What's next?</h2>
Get the source code by clicking the "Source" button on the left and start hacking!<br/><br/>

For more background on Kaa Configuration subsystem please refer to the corresponding <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Distributing+data+to+endpoints">programming guide</a> and <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Configuration">design reference</a> sections.
            ]]>
        </details>
        <platform>ANDROID</platform>
        <features>CONFIGURATION PROFILING</features>
        <sourceArchive>android/cityguide_demo.tar.gz</sourceArchive>
        <projectFolder>cityguide_demo/CityGuide</projectFolder>
        <sdkLibDir>cityguide_demo/CityGuide/libs</sdkLibDir>
        <destBinaryFile>cityguide_demo/CityGuide/bin/CityGuide-debug.apk</destBinaryFile>
    </project>
</projectsConfig>