<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>

<!--
Copyright 2014-2015 CyberVision, Inc.

  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  
  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  
  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
-->

<projectsConfig>
    <project id="cellmonitor_demo">
        <name>Cell monitor</name>
        <description>Android app demonstrating the Kaa data collection functionality</description>
        <details>
            <![CDATA[
This simple Android app illustrates time-series data collection using cell tower parameters (operator code, name, cell ID, signal strength, etc.), and the phone GPS location.

<h2>Installation</h2>
Download the .apk to your Android device by clicking the "Binary" button on the left. Make sure that the device permits installing apps from "Unknown sources". Open the downloaded apk and follow the on-screen instructions.

<h2>Playing around</h2>
Make sure that the Kaa sandbox is up and running. Opening the "Cell monitor demo" will show an activity with the latest data that the app would send over to the Kaa sandbox server.<br/><br/>

Navigate to the Kaa server administrative interface by clicking on the "Administrative console" link from the Sandbox screen. Log in as a tenant developer (devuser / devuser123), and go to to the "Cell monitor" application, then select "Schemas", "Log". Choose the latest schema version to inspect the schema of the data collected from the app.<br/><br/>

In this sample app the data is collected into a MongoDB instance. To review the configuration of the active log appender, browse to the "Log appenders" section under "Cell monitor" application, and choose "Cell monitor log appender" from the table.

<h2>What's next?</h2>
Get the source code by clicking the "Source" button on the left and start hacking!<br/><br/>

For more background on Kaa Data Collection subsystem please refer to the corresponding <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Collecting+data+from+endpoints">programming guide</a> and <a href="https://docs.kaaproject.org/display/KAA/Logging">design reference</a> sections.
            ]]>
        </details>
        <platform>ANDROID</platform>
        <features>DATA_COLLECTION</features>
        <sourceArchive>android/cellmonitor_demo.tar.gz</sourceArchive>
        <projectFolder>cellmonitor_demo/CellMonitor</projectFolder>
        <sdkLibDir>cellmonitor_demo/CellMonitor/libs</sdkLibDir>
        <destBinaryFile>cellmonitor_demo/CellMonitor/bin/CellMonitor-debug.apk</destBinaryFile>
    </project>
</projectsConfig>
